Trevor Young

trevdev.co

Phoenix, AZ

(928) 965-6426

<u>Twitter</u>

Github

trevoryoung.web@gmail.com

Replace The R Word

HTML

Raw CSS

JavaScript

Thesaurus API

GitHub Repo

Duration: 3 Days

LinkedIn

Summary:

I am a full-stack software engineer with a passion for custom, responsive styling & back-end application management. With 6 years of experience in team & project management for multiple non-profit organizations, I have learned what it takes to be successful when resources are low, time is of the essence, and fully functioning technology is essential. Whether you need a front-end designer or a full-stack developer, I have the capabilities to help you achieve your goals.

Latest Work:

Connect Direct
Vue.js Knex Express NodeJS PostgreSQL Raw CSS JavaScript JWT

Duration: 10 Days

GitHub Repo

Linked Up

React.js Redux Knex Express NodeJS PostgreSQL Bootstrap CSS JavaScript

Duration: 5 Days

GitHub Repo

gForum

HTML
Raw CSS
JavaScript
Tech Crunch API
Quote API
Knex
Express
NodeJS
PostgreSQL

Duration: 4 Days

GitHub Repo

Tech:

Redux

HTML5 CSS3 JavaScript jQuery Ajax NodeJS PostgreSQL Vue Firebase Java Python MongoDB Heroku AWS

Style:

Balsamiq Bootstrap Materialize SASS Custom CSS Pixelmator

Education:

2018 | Galvanize

Full Stack Web Development

Immersive Program

-Diversity Scholarship Award Recipient

2015 | Arizona State University

B.S. Tourism Development and Management

- -Leadership Scholarship Program
- -Cum Laude Honors

Experience:

2016-17 | Greater Phoenix Chamber Foundation

Workforce Development Program Coordinator

-Coordinated coalitions of business and educational leaders to help build the talent pipeline for Cybersecurity and IT professionals, among others.

2015-16 | Greater Phoenix Chamber of Commerce

Registration Coordinator

-Managed the Chamber's registration system for over 15 signature events.

2013-15 | Future Business Leaders of America - Arizona

Assistant State Director

-Responsible for the day-to-day operations of a non-profit student leadership organization.